Каллиграфия
«Каллиграфия»
Любовь и Смелость
Итак.
А теперь, напишите своё любимое слово
и сдайте к концу урока.
Усилие
Любовь и
Смелость
Любимое слово?
А ты что напишешь?
Скажи, трудно выбрать?
А ты уже придумала, что будешь писать?
Не-а… В голове ни одной мысли.
Точно.
Давай напишем то, что хотим попросить друг у друга.
Попросить… друг у друга?
Угу.
Идёт.
Чтобы я хотел попросить у Такаги-сан…
Дразниться запрещено
Отлично!
Будет ей намёком больше не задирать меня…
Нет… Это может вызвать обратную реакцию.
Такаги-сан такое только позабавит.
Слово, которое взовёт к её совести,
но при этом не спровоцирует…
Это не легко.
Нисиката, ты всё?
Угу.
Тогда, давай сверим?
Нейтралитет
Сдержанность
Ну как?
«Сдержанность»?
Э, ну да…
Что это? Это то, что ты хочешь от меня?
Ну, да… В какой-то степени…
О-Она не поняла.
Получается, если она не поняла,
значит всё было зря.
Подло-то как.
Кстати, а у тебя? Что означает «нейтралитет»?
А, это? Это значит…
Я хочу, чтобы Нисиката оставался таким же простачком.
Чёрт, Такаги-сан перешла в наступление!
Ясно. По таким правилам решила играть, значит.
Теперь я понял.
Может повторим ещё раз?
Идёт.
Вот увидишь, Такаги-сан.
Пришло время для моего наступления!
Закончил?
Пока, нет…
Доброта
Так я заставлю Такаги-сан понять,
что «доброта» - это не про неё.
Надеюсь тебя сильно огорчить, Такаги-сан.
Чтобы такое написать…?
Ого! Я уже трепещу, Такаги-сан.
Надеюсь, Такаги-сан,
твоё слово будет далеко от понятия «доброты».
К слову, про технику! Нисиката, у тебя отлично получается.
Выглядит забавно. Ты где-то учился каллиграфии?
Н-Нет, нигде…
Мне нравится как ты рисуешь, Нисиката.
Держи.
С-Спасибо….
Чего? Она, вдруг, стала такой добренькой…
С чего бы вдруг?
Неужели, я этого не замечал,
а Такаги-сан на самом деле милая?!
Н-Нет… Не может быть.
Уа!
Нисиката, погоди,  не дёргайся.
Э?
Соринку убрала.
Так-так, классное слово придумала.
Беготня
Мясо На Гриле
Победная кондиция
А теперь.
Нисиката, ты показываешь первым.
Э? Разве не одновременно?
Давай, давай!
Не дразни меня
В итоге, пришлось переписать.
И вправду, у тебя забавный стиль.
Э? И это всё?
В любом случае, я хочу, чтобы ты перестала дразнить меня.
Э… Ни за что!
Ты даже толком не подумала.
Хорошо. Хорошо. Я буду стараться изо всех сил.
Ну? А что у тебя?
Меня?
А у меня… вот.
У тебя на щеке клякса
В тот раз успела?
Ты же только что пообещала перестать!
Но, ведь, это случилось до обещания.
Не терять бдительность
Год 1, Класс 2, Парта 24
Нисиката
Не терять бдительность
Год 1, Класс 2, Парта 18
Такаги
Seasonal Change of Clothing Смена одежды Пересменка
"Seasonal Change of Clothing!"
Жарко…
Пожалуй соглашусь.
We should change to the
short-sleeve uniform soon. Скоро переодеваться в короткую матроску
I guess so.
I should tell Санаэ-тян we should start
wearing our short-sleeve uniforms tomorrow.
I guess so.
С чем ты там согласна?
Пред.
Aren't you guys hot? Вам разве не жарко?
What? Чего?
We said we'd all change our
uniforms at the same time! Мы же договаривались поменять форму одновременно!
We did? Правда?
We did! You jumped the gun! Правда!
I see. Сука
На следующий день
It's a lot cooler wearing short sleeves! Так и знала, так намного прохладнее
I guess so.
You guess what?
Санаэ-тян,
доброго утре… чка…
I thought you said we were all
gonna switch together?
Я забыла тебе сказать.
Legf fe hogh.
"English Translation."
That's right.
Walk down this street to the
post office and turn left there.
You will see the station.
It takes five minutes from here.
I have to get back at Такаги-сан today somehow.
What's the best way to do that?
I haven't made a jack-in-the-box in a while.
No, I don't have enough materials.
Besides, it won't be finished
in time if I start making it now.
All right, let's see…
Нисиката.
Huh? Yes, sir!
Don't "Huh? Yes, sir" me. Hurry up.
It's sixteen.
It's sixteen!
This isn't math class. It's English!
I told you to translate it!
S-Sorry, sir…
Never mind. Sit back down.
I even told you
we're on line sixteen.
Did she intentionally tell me
that so I'd get it wrong?
I didn't think you'd actually get it wrong.
I knew it.
Something on your mind?
You could say that.
What were you thinking?
Oh, it's nothing important.
Then,
were you thinking of something naughty?
Wha?!
N-No!
Really?
Of course not!
Definitely not!
I know.
You were actually thinking how to
get back at me for all the teasing I do, right?
I-I don't know what you're talking about.
I guessed right, didn't I?
You were looking my way, so I kind of figured.
If you knew, then don't ask.
It's fun to see your reactions, though.
And? Did you come up with any good ideas?
Yeah, I did. I came up with the perfect plan.
It's foolproof.
I hope you're right.
She's not worried at all.
Can she see into my mind
and realize I don't have a plan?
So? What's the plan?
A-As if I'd tell you.
Just a hint?
No… Anyway, we should
be paying attention to cla—
June 18th
Today is the eighteenth.
Такаги-сан's student
number is eighteen as well.
If I keep Такаги-сан's
attention away from class,
she might get in trouble for
not knowing where we are in the textbook.
Такаги-сан,
what did you eat for breakfast today?
Mountain yam over rice. Why?
No reason in particular.
So… you like mountain yams?
Yeah, I like them.
I feel energized the entire day
when I eat them in the morning.
I kinda get what you're saying.
What about you, Нисиката?
Me? I…
Take a guess.
Let's see.
Rice.
What do you mean, "rice"?
I didn't peg you as someone
who eats bread. Am I wrong?
No, I did eat rice, but…
It's working! Keep her attention
away from class!
Такаги-сан, you prefer rice, too?
I want someone to read from
the top of the next page.
Hmm… Today is the eighteenth, so…
Такаги.
Here we go!
Well? You don't know where we are, do you?
I will not do such a thing.
Correct.
What?!
Nice try.
Wh-What are you talking about?
Damn, she's good. I wouldn't expect
anything less from Такаги-сан.
I have to come up with another plan.
Maybe I should go on a direct
attack with a jack-in-the-box.
No, again,
I don't have the materials!
Нисиката, what's troubling you?
U-Uh… it's nothing.
Were you thinking about me again?
I-I wouldn't put it that way…
Besides, why would I be thinking about you?
Then you were thinking
about something naughty.
N-No, I wasn't!
I'm always thinking about you, though.
You're blushing.
N-No, I'm not!
You're just thinking about teasing me
like just now, aren't you?
Who knows?
What was that… momentary silence just now?
Today is June eighteenth,
and if I add the month and date
together, it's 24.
Number 24, Нисиката.
Pool
"Pool."
It's the first day we get to go in
the pool, but all I can do is watch.
If it weren't for this injured hand…
No fair. They're all having fun.
Right?
It's the first day of swimming,
and all we can do is watch. It's sad.
T-Такаги-сан, you too?
Yeah.
In your case, is it because
of your hand? What happened?
Ah, yeah…
You know, things happen.
I bet you tried to pet a stray cat
and got bitten, right?
How did you know?! I didn't tell anyone!
I'm actually right?! I just took a wild guess!
What a klutz.
Why are you just observing today—
That reminds me…
A girl who sits out swimming lessons
is usually on her period.
According to the textbook,
it causes abdominal pain.
That's what the King of Health Class, Takao, said…
Ah, it's nothing.
I shouldn't. I don't think it's something
I should be asking, anyway.
You wanted to ask why I'm not swimming today?
She heard me?!
Well, I figured out your reason
is your injured hand,
so why don't you try to guess my reason?
N-Not feeling good.
That's too vague.
No, forget it. I don't really wanna know.
Then I guess I win?
All right, I'll take a guess.
You get one try.
Though I don't think you can guess.
Damn Такаги-сан…
Is she confident because
she thinks I can't say "period"?
If that's the case, she's seriously mocking me!
No, wait!
This is Такаги-сан we're talking about.
It could be a trap!
Even if I gathered my courage and answered…
"Period!"
No, you're so rude!
That's very likely!
But knowing Такаги-сан,
she probably already knows what
I'm thinking and why I'm hesitating.
And then she'll counter that with…
You don't even know the reason
why a girl isn't swimming?
I win, then.
Is it a trap or an honest question?
Is she making it seem genuine
so I'll fall into her trap?
Or is she making it seem like
a trap but asking seriously?
This is all confusing.
Damn it. What was with that
face she made a minute ago?
Other possibilities… Like an injury?
Doesn't seem like it.
It doesn't look like she's feeling
too sick to exercise, either.
Then that would leave… No…
It's not fair. Everyone's having fun.
And I'm over here using all my brain
power battling Такаги-сан in this heat.
Нисиката, are you taking this seriously?
I think you're just looking
at the girls swimming.
N-No, I'm not!
Really?
I heard boys look at girls' chests all the time.
I said I wasn't looking.
I can't say it out loud,
but Такаги-сан doesn't really have a big chest.
I heard that a lot of small-chested girls
are pretty sensitive about it.
That's what the King of
Early Lunch, Kimura, said.
Is Такаги-сан not swimming
because she has a complex about her small chest?!
I knew it. You can't figure it out, can you?
I win today, too.
Такаги-сан, I know why.
You're concerned about
your small chest, right?
There's no way I can say that! It's beyond rude!
In the end, the only answer I have is "period."
But that's plenty rude, too.
You're still thinking? You're almost out of time.
No, it's even mentioned in the textbook.
It's nothing to be embarrassed about!
Yeah, just say it with your head held high!
All right!
The reason why you're sitting out
the swimming lesson
is that…!
You're on your period.
Wrong.
That's rude to say to a girl.
But it's mentioned in our
textbook, and usually, I…
Нисиката, you're bright red.
Then that would mean the reason is that
she has a complex about her small chest?
Too funny.
Upsy-daisy.
By the way, "too embarrassed
because of my small chest"
is also incorrect.
Wha—?!
Sensei,
I changed my mind. May I swim?
Okay.
Huh?
Then why was she watching?
Well then…
Now that I got to see Нисиката make
a good face, I guess I'll go for a swim.
Don't tell me, you were staying out
just to tease me?!
When your hand's all better…
we can swim together.
Oh, it's cold!
I won't fall for it.
When we do swim together,
she's gonna tease me again.
That's the kind of person Такаги-сан is.